Hi!
I'm Kelli.
When you're choosing a foundation, you of course want to choose a type of foundation that you're going to be the most comfortable with.
Be it a powder foundation.
These usually will work well for people who first of all, want a quick application.
Second of all, if you're a little more on the oily side, sometimes these work a little bit better for you than say a dry skin person.
You can also choose from a liquid foundation.
There's many different types of liquid foundations based on whether you're dry or you're oily or what kind of coverage you like.
There is a very wide variety of things that you can choose from.
Some of the other foundations out there, which I don't have with me today.
You can choose like a cream to powder foundation or even a mineral foundation works really well for all skins and all people.
It depends on what kind of coverage you want, what your skin's like, what kind of feel, or what kind of texture you like on your face.
Whether you're wanting more of a natural product, such as a mineral makeup or you really like the liquid foundation, or what you're more comfortable with.
Those are some different options you have when you're trying to choose the foundation that's right for you.